{
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "omoshiroi",
      "answer1":"funny",
      "answer2":"interesting",
      "answer3": "delicious",
      "answer4":"new",
      "correct": "interesting",
      "topic": "Adjectives"
    },
    {
      "question": "tanoshii",
      "answer1":"fun",
      "answer2":"enjoyable",
      "answer3": "pretty",
      "answer4":"strange",
      "correct": "enjoyable",
      "topic": "Adjectives"
    },
    {
      "question": "oishii",
      "answer1":"funny",
      "answer2":"interesting",
      "answer3": "delicious",
      "answer4":"new",
      "correct": "delicious",
      "topic": "Adjectives"
    },
    {
      "question": "atarashii",
      "answer1":"good",
      "answer2":"old",
      "answer3": "beautiful",
      "answer4":"difficult",
      "correct": "new",
      "topic": "Adjectives"
    },
    {
      "question": "yoi",
      "answer1":"good",
      "answer2":"boring",
      "answer3": "pretty",
      "answer4":"strange",
      "correct": "good",
      "topic": "Adjectives"
    },
    {
      "question": "tsumaranai",
      "answer1":"funny",
      "answer2":"interesting",
      "answer3": "boring",
      "answer4":"pretty",
      "correct": "boring",
      "topic": "Adjectives"
    },
    {
      "question": "kirei",
      "answer1":"funny",
      "answer2":"interesting",
      "answer3": "pretty",
      "answer4":"difficult",
      "correct": "pretty",
      "topic": "Adjectives"
    },
    {
      "question": "hen",
      "answer1":"good",
      "answer2":"old",
      "answer3": "strange",
      "answer4":"difficult",
      "correct": "strange",
      "topic": "Adjectives"
    },
    {
      "question": "muzukashii",
      "answer1":"funny",
      "answer2":"interesting",
      "answer3": "difficult",
      "answer4":"old",
      "correct": "difficult",
      "topic": "Adjectives"
    },
    {
      "question": "furui",
      "answer1":"new",
      "answer2":"old",
      "answer3": "beautiful",
      "answer4":"bad",
      "correct": "old",
      "topic": "Adjectives"
    },
    {
      "question": "utsukushii",
      "answer1":"good",
      "answer2":"old",
      "answer3": "beautiful",
      "answer4":"difficult",
      "correct": "beautiful",
      "topic": "Adjectives"
    },
    {
      "question": "warui",
      "answer1":"funny",
      "answer2":"bad",
      "answer3": "pretty",
      "answer4":"strange",
      "correct": "bad",
      "topic": "Adjectives"
    },
    {
      "question": "subarashii",
      "answer1":"Wonderful",
      "answer2":"Scary",
      "answer3": "Tall",
      "answer4":"Cute",
      "correct": "Wonderful",
      "topic": "Adjectives"
    },
    {
      "question": "sugoi",
      "answer1":"Cute",
      "answer2":"Fast",
      "answer3": "Hot",
      "answer4":"Convenient",
      "correct": "Amazing",
      "topic": "Adjectives"
    },
    {
      "question": "suteki",
      "answer1":"Small",
      "answer2":"Kind",
      "answer3": "Splendid",
      "answer4":"Large",
      "correct": "Wonderful",
      "topic": "Adjectives"
    },
    {
      "question": "takai",
      "answer1":"Tall",
      "answer2":"Short",
      "answer3": "Fast",
      "answer4":"Convenient",
      "correct": "Tall; High; Expensive",
      "topic": "Adjectives"
    },
    {
      "question": "hayai",
      "answer1":"Young",
      "answer2":"Slow",
      "answer3": "Strict",
      "answer4":"Thin; Slender",
      "correct": "Fast; Quick",
      "topic": "Adjectives"
    },
    {
      "question": "kibishii",
      "answer1":"Strict",
      "answer2":"Kind",
      "answer3": "Wonderful",
      "answer4":"Convenient",
      "correct": "Strict",
      "topic": "Adjectives"
    },
    {
      "question": "nagai",
      "answer1":"Small",
      "answer2":"Large",
      "answer3": "Long",
      "answer4":"Cute",
      "correct": "Long",
      "topic": "Adjectives"
    },
    {
      "question": "kakkoii",
      "answer1":"Young",
      "answer2":"Trendy; Cool",
      "answer3": "Thin; Slender",
      "answer4":"Fast",
      "correct": "Trendy; Cool",
      "topic": "Adjectives"
    },
    {
      "question": "yasashii",
      "answer1":"Warm",
      "answer2":"Strict",
      "answer3": "Kind; Gentle",
      "answer4":"Cheap; Inexpensive",
      "correct": "Kind; Gentle",
      "topic": "Adjectives"
    },
    {
      "question": "atatakai",
      "answer1":"Cute",
      "answer2":"Short",
      "answer3": "Warm",
      "answer4":"Large",
      "correct": "Warm",
      "topic": "Adjectives"
    },
    {
      "question": "mijikai",
      "answer1":"Tall",
      "answer2":"Long",
      "answer3": "Short",
      "answer4":"Small",
      "correct": "Short",
      "topic": "Adjectives"
    },
    {
      "question": "hosoi",
      "answer1":"Short",
      "answer2":"Large",
      "answer3": "Thin; Slender",
      "answer4":"Cold",
      "correct": "Thin; Slender",
      "topic": "Adjectives"
    },
    {
      "question": "osoi",
      "answer1": "fast",
      "answer2": "slow",
      "answer3": "new",
      "answer4": "old",
      "correct": "slow",
      "topic": "Adjectives"
    },
    {
      "question": "yuumei",
      "answer1": "famous",
      "answer2": "unknown",
      "answer3": "shy",
      "answer4": "loud",
      "correct": "famous",
      "topic": "Adjectives"
    },
    {
      "question": "tsumetai",
      "answer1": "hot",
      "answer2": "cool",
      "answer3": "warm",
      "answer4": "cold",
      "correct": "cool",
      "topic": "Adjectives"
    },
    {
      "question": "yasui",
      "answer1": "expensive",
      "answer2": "cheap",
      "answer3": "large",
      "answer4": "small",
      "correct": "cheap",
      "topic": "Adjectives"
    },
    {
      "question": "wakai",
      "answer1": "old",
      "answer2": "young",
      "answer3": "mature",
      "answer4": "childish",
      "correct": "young",
      "topic": "Adjectives"
    },
    {
      "question": "benri",
      "answer1": "inconvenient",
      "answer2": "comfortable",
      "answer3": "annoying",
      "answer4": "unimportant",
      "correct": "convenient",
      "topic": "Adjectives"
    },
    {
      "question": "ookii",
      "answer1": "big",
      "answer2": "small",
      "answer3": "tall",
      "answer4": "short",
      "correct": "big",
      "topic": "Adjectives"
    },
    {
      "question": "chiisai",
      "answer1": "big",
      "answer2": "small",
      "answer3": "short",
      "answer4": "tall",
      "correct": "small",
      "topic": "Adjectives"
    },
    {
      "question": "atsui",
      "answer1": "cold",
      "answer2": "hot",
      "answer3": "wet",
      "answer4": "dry",
      "correct": "hot",
      "topic": "Adjectives"
    },
    {
      "question": "samui",
      "answer1": "hot",
      "answer2": "cold",
      "answer3": "wet",
      "answer4": "dry",
      "correct": "cold",
      "topic": "Adjectives"
    },
    {
      "question": "kawaii",
      "answer1": "ugly",
      "answer2": "beautiful",
      "answer3": "disgusting",
      "answer4": "cute",
      "correct": "cute",
      "topic": "Adjectives"
    },
    {
      "question": "kowai",
      "answer1": "brave",
      "answer2": "fearful",
      "answer3": "happy",
      "answer4": "sad",
      "correct": "fearful",
      "topic": "Adjectives"
    },
    {
      "question": "kowai",
      "answer1": "brave",
      "answer2": "fearful",
      "answer3": "happy",
      "answer4": "sad",
      "correct": "fearful",
      "topic": "Adjectives"
    },
    {
      "question": "kowai",
      "answer1": "brave",
      "answer2": "fearful",
      "answer3": "happy",
      "answer4": "sad",
      "correct": "fearful",
      "topic": "Animals"
    },
    {
      "question": "kowai",
      "answer1": "brave",
      "answer2": "fearful",
      "answer3": "happy",
      "answer4": "sad",
      "correct": "fearful",
      "topic": "Numbers"
    },
    {
      "question": "kowai",
      "answer1": "brave",
      "answer2": "fearful",
      "answer3": "happy",
      "answer4": "sad",
      "correct": "fearful",
      "topic": "Greetings"
    },
    {
      "question": "kowai",
      "answer1": "brave",
      "answer2": "fearful",
      "answer3": "happy",
      "answer4": "sad",
      "correct": "fearful",
      "topic": "Verbs"
    },
    {
      "question": "kowai",
      "answer1": "brave",
      "answer2": "fearful",
      "answer3": "happy",
      "answer4": "sad",
      "correct": "fearful",
      "topic": "School"
    },
    {
      "question": "kowai",
      "answer1": "brave",
      "answer2": "fearful",
      "answer3": "happy",
      "answer4": "sad",
      "correct": "fearful",
      "topic": "General"
    }
  ]
}
